DARYNA FESYK

darynafesyk@gmail.com | +46760565781 | Margaretaplatsen 6, Helsingborg

SUMMARY

I am experienced UX/UI designer with passion and great knowledge of front-end development. I specialise in designing and building captivating web pages with prioritizing the users experience, also I design dynamic banners and interactive advertisements . I am really excited to be a part of a team that I can present my creative new design ideas.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UX-designer assistant, BetterMe

Oct 2020 - Feb 2022

- Creating mockups, wireframes and prototypes
- Making sure that webpages are accesible for all, A/B testing
- Assisted in communication with customers, helped to understand their needs, goals, and behaviors

Webb designer, ST Graphics

June 2020 - Sep 2020

- Developing and designing webpages
- Creating custom graphics, such as logos and icons, for a wide variety of products and websites.
- · Communicating with clients, presenting mockups
- Communicating with the rest of the team, making sure everything is made along with clients wants.

Freelance as React.js website developer

Apr 2023 - now

- Creating a websites from scratch, starting with design and up development, testing, deployment, managing DNS, domains and payment system integrations.
- Creating e-commerce websites
- Communication with clients directly, making sure every detail is included.

EDUCATION

Kiev National economic University

Jan 2019 - Feb 2022

Finance, economics, markering

SCVOT

Jan 2018 - Dec 2019

UX/UI design

Sundgården Folkhögskola

Jan 2023 - June 2023

Front-end development

KEY SKILLS

- Figma, Sketch, Canva, Webflow
- HTML, CSS, SASS
- React.js, Node.js,
- Corporate communications.
- Problem solving.
- Customer service.
- · Attention to details.
- Fluent in English, conversational Swedish